Jhaal
Hello friends, I am Piyush Patel.
Greetings to all of you from Profits to Meet
I heartily welcome you to today's session.
Friends, today we will update you on the result.
Add New Result Start Getting Pregnant
Friends, you are done with annual pimples.
We get finals guys who
You guys also track the annual results of the company
It is not necessary to see the result
We will make it, we will decide the gender
Companies and sectors where investing
It should be pre-decided light
And for this, last Sunday we first
You get great companies and great sectors
Details about it and what to expect from it
Keep that also with you guys Milind Bhai and Jai
Kishan ji had told me friends
That your company, under the sector, is your foot now.
As the results come in and if the results
If it comes as per your expectation
This gives you guidance on what to do next.
Should the vantage be increased or should the weightage be
If it is shifted a little somewhere else then this
Friends, with guidance, we are providing remedies.
People will discuss this oil company today.
Friends, today's radio is needed along with the paper.
what is our schedule
that this presentation is by some students
has made it, tell me your disclosure
Check the data yourself before buying two Edisons.
Who is it friends, it could be a student
So investors like you get the first piece
The doctor is going to update its result
Hetal Basic from Suraj HDFC
Chirag is about to update the bank results
Hal who is from Rajkot and has an IPL contract
If the minimum balance is Rs. then its result
Presenting Mayank Shah Pump Indoor
The company data that three students had
collected, researched, and estimated
that we will share with our friends
MP3 To Guide All Students
Dr Milan Bidve from Pune is
All three were busy with the students, so today
The doctor will not meet with us in the meeting
will be able to come because of Kuna a little
Bend over the load hanging we know friends
What challenging times are you all going through right now, friends?
People Gurjar Rai, you are a [ __ ]
Million brothers might have died in the accident.
So no doubt we are doing very well.
Data with your three students from
I could have done research but I am not able to meet him and
Jai Kishan ji in place of Milan Bhai
Sanjay Kishan ji is with you all from Dubai.
I am going to provide tips results but
Jackson while the teams results later but
Let's get that changed today with Jackson's
chatting
Lot let me backup this is from Jai Kishan ji
Dubai so tujhe question ka me introduce
I will make you a post graduate.
Already done
Ajay Kumar in System Management and
Certified International Credit Professional
They were very interested in the city last week.
One is in stock market research and
If you like to watch cricket and football then let's go
I welcome Jai Kishan ji or change
Thank yourself very much to every one of us
Increase Hiper Points in this Challenge Time
For the question lots of everything with all
In Gujarat in India and all over India
If your student projects then the result
We will introduce it later, let's find out.
Which companies did these people work for?
I have done some work, can you help me?
The bed was like last week we
People had given the review that Boko Haram
Steven expects more from the company
Yes, you will meet and I have unquestionably
You should have received that commitment by today.
If the correct one is not presented then their
The team has done a great job and today
There are companies that have already declared results.
declares about the same
The first company to give the team its side is Tata
Consultancy Services Next is HDFC
Why Bank Panther Debit Person Company
Because I bought it from 15 companies and then from another company.
Why aren't you guys bothering the company?
And this is the same company
Heaven of this three company is strong
They have leaders in their system.
Consistency is this period of time
Andesha Basically Quality Companies and Chief
Daughter's Pet Wealth You Need to Be An
Quality Companies Which Have Brought Some
Quality plus growth is equal to wealth
Tax applicants should expect
Top Quality Company and Leading on Jayanti
Computer room sector and what is the region
Off
* See Prevent Questions to Your Love
From Our Students' Festival Mike and Wall
With user Kishan ji, now whom first?
You will invite Dr. Atul first.
Will raise Desai but gift introduction
About after this three-day strike
Child specialist from Surat some night
Indiscriminate medical profession for more
Interactive Features He Hens Very Keen
Interest in any feedback reading surrounded
Tha in himself as a very good doctor
also ok his wife is geeta and she does a
Doctor Ko Hips Doctor Sahab Also Visited
Her Work Entries Death is Sun and Water
without much for two hours request after
His Death Literature
How to present tune TCS researchers and
Lips event has made the expectation sort
of
That Tanu when this help Mittal Bhai jis big
It is a very challenging time for you during the Corona period.
People want this too, isn't it?
Video Lokayukta and in that also you have to
Did research and protest on salary today
I am moving towards prosperity or manic depression
We have kept these three companies
After the performance, you will be in your section.
This is how I will have to go
Hospital, no problem, but your data is there.
Jeera Bhai, answering queries on your behalf
I'll make a change I'll mute myself
I give Jai Kishan ji and energy welcome
edelweiss ok thank you
Hello friends, this is the series of Indian Result.
Welcome all of you to our Last Sunday
Captain and Vice Captain custom milling and a
The option was given to you in the history.
that what our hope is inheritance so you
We will turn it around to ensure it lives up to expectations.
Did it come down or not, sir had taught us that
How likely are we to read the truth or
how much David is making from that and he
You got the idea by looking at the presentation.
If the beginning is like this then what will be the style
The presentation was very impressive, let's see it now.
How those companies behave one by one
does
Hello friends, it has been a year since someone
The second running ovation to This Is My Life
has completely changed so in this case my
Friend and psychiatrist is famous doctor of Surat
Mukul Joshi, I remember two of his lines.
If she knows Gujarati, then definitely do mehndi.
I will give it to you
And password protected Shola Bani Rakhi
Surgeon and password protected Shola became Rakhi.
Sajanwa digital thee jaan hod kareena cheetah sajanwa
Meaning, it is the pain of the city that its beloved
Because of the people and because of the distance
I am meeting them and with my feelings
If she is not showing it, then she is in pain and
We all may not be naans, so what if we are
Yes, we are interested in what we would think.
Brother, which sector is this even in bad times?
something that is resilient that can survive or
Even in such bad times, the growth of the opposite
We can start such sector based companies
We will look for someone who sees the opportunity and hits a four
They should screen my sector for us.
My company is from A sector.
She belongs to the friends with whom she talks.
I have been in the IT sector, we saw the last
In march and benefit was breaking so deal with.
cut
There was a lot of preparation in the index and I showed this much.
Not broken, recovery also came first and breakup
I have already given the tuition teacher and now a new one is coming.
If it is continuously going then a little bit of that sector
Let's talk about the IT sector as a part of our GDP.
contributes about one percent and
He will contribute up to 50% in the coming years.
This is our estimate of the world's
It Works
India means this is a very big industry
It is a mature industry for us, but still
If there is growing then in our grinder
How Interested Should Invest Robuses Be
And now I'm so big
There are many companies in the industry
If so, why be in a hurry because
When we go down, we first see that
TCS 68th choice by market
Even the market comments, meaning the market
He is 70% more addicted to computers.
All other companies are different, their mouths are different.
Although we have listed the top five and six companies
Trophy company is a little bit about everyone.
Can't talk about the finance company
So its sales are 1.6 lakh crores which is its
Sixty percent more than near-stupidity
It is a matter of happiness that Master
Our sales this year are Rs 1 lakh crore.
Fresh for the one who has joined the club
Its profit must also be approximately
20 thousand crores have been reached but still our
The team is sixty percent bigger than it was in the beginning.
is his
Now we do a bigger business on this.
IT companies don't have pain
He has different companies, Kesari company.
The net profit margin is also very good.
is around twenty percent and
Secondly, this is India's private
The largest job-providing company in the sector
And it has 0.8 million workers working for it.
This is a very big figure, so this
It is also very large in terms of
and its long-term performance PM see
So its sales vote in the last 20 years is 20%
Even if we look at the 10 year period, it has increased by 20%.
Profit has increased by 6217%
This is a lot of comments, this much for 20 years.
Providing consistent growth is no small matter
There are not that many lights on the base either.
Secondly, its sales in a single year are huge.
It hasn't been down for a single year.
It is a very big deal, so all this
Considering the scale, we consider TCS
When we conduct elections, will someone tell me that Sir, these
Why no fees? We have heard that IPO
Someone invested money in Infosys at the time of
He bet five and became a millionaire, so friends
I would like to say that history repeats.
Itself who has done it today, he does TCS.
TCS has been quite late in the IPO market
I came and said that yesterday's meeting was very late, by the way 50
Playlist is a year old company
It happened first and even after that he destroyed your wealth
I have generated it, I will come now brother.
Five, we have seen that it is glorious and
President what is the current train that our
What is the brother of Main Interest doing now?
Azad's here nearby, but what about now?
How is this, if I talk about my mind
Sales fell by just two percent, A felt this
So it fell, brother, but at that time our
GDP is weakened by 25 percent
If you are not happy in front then nothing will happen to you.
Time to let us know, Care Investor
Brother, this is a resident company, this is breaking
It is not going to happen and it will record soon.
Breakup will give electricity, one makes that flat
It had happened in the ninth that he opposed 2%
And last Sunday we did space that
This five percent must come from its source.
And in one report also the same is around 4.6
I felt very good after listening to the scent which was beyond our expectations.
is around
become
break down
A bit of her in the hospital is 14%
I recorded a little bit as the situation came along and
Temple Run breaks the name and tells Paun
Percent means Hari almost achieved that record
He will do this, we hope, so that we do not
It was estimated that it would remain flat but
Almost flat, up 135%
So our expectation is around
should be in
when they come under
This is what happened to the current train which was looted by us.
Expect liked running around so
In such a situation, investors, what is our next?
What is the future expectation of
Friends, we hope that in the coming
TCS sales have grown by 50% in the past few years.
This will generate profit growth from voting percentage.
Our hope is that by 2030, we will be around 30-31.
This company is among the top two-three companies in India.
The one that will make sales of Rs 10 lakh crore will be Lions.
will enter the club and at that time her
The profit he makes today is Rs 1.6 crore.
The profit she will make is approximately 1.5 pips 1.6
lakh crore which will be a huge achievement
And his internship price at that time was around 8
And these entrance prizes will be around 10
We are very conservative, but
that this year's scent intensifies its
Twelfth class is kept nearby and at that time
Expect number 101 came to your mind
The question will arise that let them start.
I bought it but now we are at a lower level to buy it.
don't want
Using technical support to buy
who taught us tuition
If it is, then it is in rallying mood right now, then
From now on they teach us to wait in the railing
to do when the company is down a little bit
Give correction then we will do it for 1 minute
Its range is between 22 to 25 26
Hmm, let's start doing that in a minute, now we're home.
comes back a little closer to him
Will buy intensify his 204 come on him
Such a possibility is very rare, once in a decade
Like the lastic I had blown, I got a chance
This opportunity does not come again and again, so this
Accurate in the range of 22 to 25 and 26
And as I said, its long-term
The target will be the same weight ask by 2030.
We have set a target for our information.
This cell
Stay tuned for profit-making
This is not for long term trading
So what's the confusion
That's a little below as I described it.
I have a little husband in management that he
Some new ones in the school with pensions in retail
launching the platform over there and that
If they expand their services, it will increase their revenue.
And the problem will increase, this is good for us.
If it is a matter then it will come to more confusion brother.
If we discussed it, what confusion did we have?
If you can remove it, please must have company.
For every point a teacher has added to his portfolio
The flame should be its location.
You can do up to five to seven percent and the lock
Ministers are earning, it is only for them
Accordingly, you should keep buying every month
Their minutes should be kept and investors
MLC came who solved one of our problems.
Those in the family will know its full form.
Form Life From
Incremental income means it will last you lifelong.
She will prepare a bill and will also give division and capital
If she also gives appreciation then it will be for our children.
I have to hold on to that side my whole life.
We have to keep you with us in our old age and
You will become our support like our child.
So this was behind the asthma prank. Very much.
that the terrorists' doctor Khetal is no brilliant
Sama Popup TCS and It's Thank You For
Dating Show The Tips For Patients Leading
Companies in India India IT Sector and
Just like you, a goat is during this
Is your time and this is already giving me
All the most intense free runes and observed
This Ruled Written Station Amazing Company Tube
Rohit Roy has been all over the screen with his
According to Jin Kishan ji, if he is in an IT company
And we can do anything but why TCS
I would love to hear this
He gave a lot of weightage that he never
Bigg Boss never happened to them
So if this company makes huge profit from the condition
If tax is being paid then if you have it with us
that we can definitely keep the company that we
Also, there is a question in our back about the condition.
So come and invest in such a company.
People from all around see me as Krishna Ji.
That 50% of the companies have yet to launch
If it makes a profit then don't expect anything from it.
Can we have consistency like this year?
The officer tried to like it in dividends.
The investment which does not give dividend
Son, give it to me, I have given you a lukewarm song
But I think it depends on the people involved.
Whereas if they are hired at such a company, then they
One should also expect good results
Competition because now it is a question of the company
Enough is enough, so now this company is Fifty
Dentists can do more than 100 percent
is on
Loot So what is the next company so that
You have tree company this play leader n
The X Factor in Private Banking
Whose village is quite good and in the coming times
More renewable growth is expected in time as well.
HDFC Bank in this from 20 companies
Will be presented by the good people
Govind Chirag Goyal is from Badho Dum Hussain
Officer in Bank Point Co of Baroda
Isn't that the motor spirit of fifty-seven
years old and is already planning for
his retirement s60 sooryavansh earthquake on this
Sent and After on the website Almost 8
Sixty, he has to travel the whole world in the morning
This is plots on this very clear and his
Targets Already Sent His Soldiers Wear
Satisfied Credit Professional and Without
Much and you but welcome Iraq war and
Pure Team Leader Forest Team
Jai Hind Jai Kisan C
Sir, you should watch the movie Apna Jalwa.
Hello hello, how about looking at the cool twins?
The picture is
Sir, this is my twin, just like the ATM.
If we talk about this Gypsy market then
PCS is the number one government in India
So at number three, like all these qualities
Please tell me the actual time and I will copy and paste it immediately.
There is no change, so it makes sense
If there is a change after removing it then the target of the pocket will change.
No, you will see something here, this is TMC
TCS is the leader of private banks.
The area is here to select this serum
If you do then three, then after that this is for them.
Whatever happens in the market, in the world
He is the top Twenty20 match in India and is third in the list.
The largest drawback is their finance sector.
I have a big name like Tips Life
Tips TMC Stacy Keibler Pregnancy
Housing finance from this zip in care
We had a break with the SDM and here we are talking.
If you do, private sector hinge stickers
It is important that the successes in China
Whoever is from somewhere else has a profit of Rs 1 lakh crore.
doing five of I's in 10 and
Tag us along with the sacred fire of India
Recipe apps time will increase we will protest
GDP MPs make profits of Rs 1 lakh crore
It will reach here, see Sir of the industry
There are about 19 companies which are yet to register.
But out of that, eight percent of the market
Promotions are low SDFC Bank Kotak
Bank ICICI Bank Crush Log 4 on 9
know and will operate in these four
In this we will discuss why this situation is happening.
Here you will see that
40 questions from the context above
were up
to Ajay
That only SDFC Bank has 40% of the market
It will be known about the revenue of
80 crore class is 5th Avenue and that two
How to Bank and HDFC Bank Price
So we will wonder what State Bank was taking
So this time it feels like these sides
In profit, you will know that one and a half lakh
Saheb Minutes and 11000 products in crores
It does white specific market
I will see that the best margin is because
This bank should raise this little percentage to the mayor.
Problem Margin around Chatra Parishad
and their business is half of that, 50,000 rupees on the contrary
If it is made then here on the table
It's all down to
Let's talk about quality
And here you will see the returns.
HDFC Bank's best on equity
But the most important area is
LPA in the area is that it is as low as
If that return is not coming then the lowest
Secrets Steps Gets 126 Delights
Sir, I believe that the young man is a private
Banking in but India's saree with me
This is the least such American professor has ever seen.
know all pervasive like where you anti a
Meaning how many comments have been made and what is this
Where does it get lost in the middle of his heart at that very moment
His back is the highest at three and a half percent.
And if we talk about its seeds, then the most
1 lakh 75 thousand crores, then there should be records of it.
I haven't used it in 20 years.
That and this are not like that together, great company
Like we did it from 2010 to 2015
Take it and grind it, I have seen other profits.
So it was found that in the last five years or 10
I like my breasts like that during the fasting year
It has been around now we are reducing this by 20%.
has never happened
That they consistently give you a Bieber piece
I've never made friends so strong that I can bite them.
You will not get your profit from this system also.
Sometimes the system is not done, so it's like
You have to keep TCS like this, that's why
If anyone wants to see it, we can take it to him.
See any current for a year
give it to me
So, as if water was being formed there, you know
that who was everyone's people then also his
There was no system in India, 25 percent hidden
Put Whey Protein Set from Delight
Note that till now you have maintained it under 6%
I also did not do 6%, Ramesh had clarified
that this year ends up at five percent
It will keep an eye on it and this is actually
I have got a small cross in the profit
We will see
It's the birthday of
That world famous pop knows the whole of India
This question has never been raised in the country
If there are bandages then it is an amazing thing and
The same profit was not made but not maintained.
have done
said that the king was 1965 one day more and
We finally selected Chakradharpur at 15
I agree that it costs a little less because of the cement.
So 15 will come but actually
This gave us problems 18 Bachchan's
I have given the return and this is today's talk of Neelam
If we can get cash from this in the future
come into it
I have shown it in full here.
His 20 years of grinding have been around the likes
In which he explained why he came into the cockpit.
We have done a complete analysis of the 2017 shades of Pet Sub
Amazon by combining and doing Star Industry
Everything we did last time we met again
declared that the presentation would then appear
So those kids let's also tell everyone
You will find it in the description there
You can see its entirety from this and we are going to take a look at the current situation.
Speaking of, 20 fans from Continuum
Many properly are essential so we
If we expect it to be 20% then here
Accounts will also be seen to be 60 by 2030
There could be a cess of Rs 7.5 crore on crore.
And the profit is also Rs 1.40 lakh crore.
The highest around when satisfied PCS
This marriage will continue and we will talk about next year.
So here we see that the source of 6%
Your struggle can be liked and
We send fifteen percent of the profit
can
Business worth Rs 60,000 crore and Rs 35 lakh were looted.
TCS has made a profit of thousands of crores.
Tamil Nadu's business is little in the state.
Your profit margin is good
And in terms of profit it should increase by 19%.
will go for the long term and this company
The special thing is its voting pattern.
Then he will see patterns from this old time
10 experiments were done just here the promoter's
If you like 120 things then visit Irfan's portal
This means we have become Indian, our retail
We have been segmented and all of us have become Muslims.
Mix all this PM masking and drink it.
Twenty-five percent is his birthday and who is he?
I am Vikram, those people are our company
But I am so confident that it will make so much money.
We are the ones who give it to you from here and we are giving it to you.
Cut it and throw it away as many people as possible
The only words needed
Talking about MP4, here
You got to see around thirteen hundred
His impact was lost in the last two matches
It is going through correction and this opinion is also time
Also said a little below the guys from the last match
Aim to look trans and give her the most
Even after the reduction between 1000 and late tears
He gets fever in such a quantity that
minutes and its long-term one year
is targeted is around 1830 and it
Hereditary is now a plate time when result
It has been declared so I have told you some things about tomatoes.
Importance of Banking
Whatever can be said in the sector, one thing is very
If one believed his record, it would have been a little
It gets faster, both these things are still incomplete.
I just mentioned that in China in the last
Lokpal has had its largest number of people in this year.
Those who come out will have problems and whatever happens
There is little in requesting him
The problem is Jean
Khairthal particular topic like reference
The police have become electronic, everything has gone
Selling things during difficult times and simultaneously
People first put a little credit card in it
and reduced it by debiting it
Because of this, there is a slight effect on his set.
And when we talk about the other side, its condition
MP is behind him, this is what the group has done.
It has to be done but the Supreme Court was involved
Last year from March 1st to 30th
By August 1st, anyone can climb a mountain.
I will stay downstairs and see if anyone wants to visit him.
Any person due to his financial condition
People call it quantity bodies in these
I don't want to get pregnant and that next time
You go along and then his Jain
and removed the 30th century to make it 30
Plus it is till March 2019, which means right now MP
How much to do and how professionally to do it
While that thing is not in the hands of BSP,
Supreme Court is a problem for white people.
The second one follows
I can wear it to the office because of that trust.
Neither has the second experiment been done because of
I also said that some time is coming
Honey can be difficult and will be the leader
that it takes a little effort and that is why those
I don't know when I was robbed, there's no need on the stairs.
Yes, but it is small, that was the matter then, but the room
Better than this and we take Akshat and flowers for ₹5
Like to take it easy and do it long term
Thank you, thank you, go
That's brilliance like the way you explained it.
that it is another consistent compounder
Do PCS and if in it's a very good
Companies to have in your portfolio and
Private Sector Banks OK Now Kuwait
Because of this the slide is important Pappu Sir
Which is the status of private sector banks
Chest Hamir Singh Jis To Give One Example
has been
Explain that PSU banks together account for 60%
Updates and reviews are 60% of total revenue.
PSU Banks and Testing and Quality
3232 percent is to private banks in the
The next 3 years will see me reversing 6
Pro VS Private Banks and Almost
32.4 Fixed PSU Banks as You Can See
How this good player wants and I think with
* X-ray testing marks vote on questions
Banks Fit Clip CR Tiffin Eyes * Insurance
Area
A brilliant thanks thanks Chirag torn torn
Wonderful app see settings let's move on if
you should give you want to hide anything on
That Ajay Krishna ji 1124 presentation and
Chirag too and reported dead
whose to
that the company considers Western and Indian
Industry One has the largest presence in IT and
One is the largest private bank in
Waiting for long time in this company
But only 1000 feet you to say that in
India can we are going to see companies will
Make profits of fifty thousand crores in
Coming time now is because waterfalls are in front
Of may zinc coming for years only by fire.
Nor is he doing his long back for five
Years paid in the World Bank
President Ring in this Alliance Clubs of
Fifty thousand crore profit in that
Very high for students in my their
Country and use High Court should endeavor in
long-term in.com small companies earthquake
Recent Years Actors Rang Royi Thi
500 1000 Sir Sir Name Let's move on to the
Not just one from the Next company, Dissolve
Company from a drama growing sector and
It's a leader in inspector is ICICI
Lombard at Noida will be presented to
You've always been a master in the meantime
computers and have started his career as
A Consultant Currently Working and Don't Know
She also has fixed Coolpad wife in whose
Present [ __ ] end joint profit prominent
Tool to help him good his school to VPN
Sharif Feel
that clips in knowledge sharing learning new
things and traveling with his family and
Friends, please request Mr. Director General
Police Present Vash Loot Weather A
Thank you Jai Kishan ji Kaur and Wedding Collection
Thank you friends, today I am at ICICI
Lombard General Insurance which is the company
I will discuss about it in length.
Before that, let me ask you all a question.
I want general insurance to be our
This is how much a country expresses in GDP
This is a very important question that we need to know
Friends, I just want to tell you
Point 9 4 6 in our GDP
He contributes to the entire general
Why is the insurance sector like this?
Emergent sector is a new sector friends this
Point percentage in India so that we know
would like to know how much up to nine percent of it
General Insurance contributes
Sectors in the US
How much does it cost in China, up to 2.1%
If he contributes then according to this
If you look at it, friends, it is quite good here.
There are possibilities of growth in this sector and
Find any country from developing and
This sector goes to the developed state
Use rage has been seen in friends point and
Launched that your favorite one company doctor.
Baghat Ray, our all-weather company,
She also belongs to the same sector.
Let's see the business in the sector friends.
How is this India Indian system?
If we have performed then we are in the Indian sector
Look, these were public sector banks.
He is an Om Public Sector Company and 1% of that
Barham Private is protesting from Syria.
If we look at the sectors, then 12% overall sector
We can divide it into three parts
General insurance is a health insurance.
But let's sew a special one on it.
flashlights of tractors
Agriculture is what the word agriculture
Insurance does it, now we go to the company
Towards that before that one of you friends
I would like to ask you a question, can you tell me?
That companies are listed for our tractors
Inside
Hello friends, I would like to tell you all
There is only one company which provides general insurance.
State Bank of India's General Insurance is in this sector.
I mean why is it so friends that there is only one
company it is a company because sir
Here's a company that puts profitability first
I am in and in opposition this is because like sir if
I want to tell you every day about this company
Android 2.3 is the leader, up 50% since 2004
The city is one among its private players
In this the accused is between 90% and 20% and
There was a significant change in the sector
Last year it was 34 percent.
Activation required for Twenty505 stations
Now let's talk about solvency countries.
This is a very important tractor which we
Insurance companies should keep this
That Sir, wow, the minimum line is IIT.
1.5 Versace company notes this year
She is deleting point 293 extra
Now let's talk about it, posted here
So now we can see that the company
Profit margin support at 90 per cent
The average is long years, but why is that because
If there are emerging tractors then through them
Emerging into a strong tractor while remaining short
This company of companies is locked in this
We need a good treatment, now we move ahead.
Let's see what happens in current affairs
what happened milk something important here
Point when our GD was on - 25%
This factor up to negative fenugreek - 5 per cent
When we recovered well from it, this company
Growth had come down to one percent in the ninth
We had to look at that percentage.
against and we had distinguished this
Sales growth of like five percent
We need company at our express station
Perfect clear stand is done and
Premium growth of boyfriend in this we
But Prince watches more because this
Company Manager Sales Important Only
The tractor is premium, we call it
If you look at the premium, there
The result we have applied is perfect
If we talk about profit then profit also went away.
Consistent Cheese 20% 42% 20.91 We have this
But saffron is 28.4 but it has come that thirty percent
B Option Provisions This is because of the fold and
For this reason, but still our expectations
that it is just as per the rules and its results are now
Friends, I want to tell you only on that point.
I wish we were what we expected
What is Aya and K Express
We can celebrate Eid like we did this year
Expected that Polythene Thousand
This crore company should grow
The results should come and from this question of ours
Better for 30 minutes cars have come and
Friends, keeping this in mind, we will achieve this in 2030.
You can get more information from the company that For Twenty
Will cross thousand crore sales
This premium premium is targeted at
Talk about premium sales
Talking about profitability, here we
To cross routes up to fifteen hundred
Target was admitted but company near about.
Just four weeks ago, he made a profit of Rs 100 crore.
which is our question is free and
Keeping this in mind, we are now targeting 2019.
Look at us, we are worth a thousand crores.
I surpass the profitability of this company
We will see in 2030, friends, one point
But
Torch will be like high from highly profitable
If there is profit then the sector has only one life.
We should put it up, we have written that I am in your shadow.
If there is profit then the reserve price of the company
Yes, that should also be high, let's drink tea today
If we take it we can see the chart piers
This is the cup and a half moving stock as we know it.
That is the latest offer for your tractor and this is
Up and movie stock is there that if the phone
If you look at it friends, look how sharp it is.
Recovery has been done, you can do this in the next vote only.
Now more than almost sixty percent
I had recovered and my stomach had also come in it.
Just currently, if we now talk about its bike price
If we talk then we should do this for 1 minute.
Chapter must have a company
Because this is a very growing sector.
Emergent Leadership Long-Term Work We Its
This computer must have a location
We were perfect here for a relationship.
Inside Activision and the upcoming Dynasty
If we want a target, we can keep it at 100 feet.
Friends, this company is about long-term wealth.
Creation is a company in which we have long term
value will be created and money will be made, therefore
say that from the previous word and subscribe
Definitely Company Leadership Profit Margin
This company will recover in the coming time.
And we need
launching company so right now we three
No more than 100% pimples interest
It should be kept because Amar Singh is there so some
while taking a puff and the second thing is if there is any time
These are the insurance plans available now
Therefore, do Kundalini channel for 1 minute.
Try to side with this in your
I'll wrap up the presentation a little bit and
I will call Jai Kishan ji, thank you sir.
Why should we consider this thing brilliant Sun?
Expecting This Company to Be an Internet Teacher
In the general insurance sector and definitely
Like Boot See The Future Of This Company Agree
1950 Thanks for your support for
Prediction and Predictions for the Future
Off
Confirmation of If You Want to Hide Anything
Else 280 Sensitive Verification Form End
Definitely Ad Man Kills Pet I Think Last
Year During Discussion Veeravratam Discussing
A Life Insurance Company Oriental
University 2ND Year Wish To SBI Entry
Soft today may not have staked their life
I will change, Uday Bihar was a friendly person
Giving us a feedback number in eyes she
Developed Countries General Insurance Company
Doing So They Can Expect Channel
That general insurance company Ruby Movie Kahel To
Der and other company which we can do cutting
List World Exists Only One Company
Yes I Think Woman by Harshit Khushbu
Invented co david persson to be given a good
They take a
in this
that this is a normal top o
Dumri percent son of Kishan ji Bhai Compound
And all this representation of can go chili
527 percent vests in TCS Sterlite
Sab Khayaal University Sheden Na
Investment Will IT Consulting Software
and be completed
That your under-51 Shudra is the same Ramkudi
Requesting for This and Tissue Twist
Transferred into TCS and Infosys and
Garhwal Sector Sector Destroy This Should
Invest in Infosys
translocation of her husband Hansa Quality
Infosys two of three percent balance sheet
18234 St TCS Wipro TCS or 5757
The More You Have Invested in Love You Can Have
Invested in emerging industries and mid
Beaten by wicket interested in doing
Industry in Coming Years Back When Alone
With consisting of Bihar in this thank you
All Subscribe To
Which women's company statuses have come
Out and the modal list institution and in
Line with What We've Been Expecting
Toe Protecting R Add Sauveer
Verification into several requests of
Time in Just 120 Days
Wanna man let me an act
Impotent you went on next Sunday we are
Going Quiet Check Manager
that urinal idea go into account the wake of
Which company here in inch less next and
Taylor Main Companies Which Are Going to Result
I have come but to Bihar * Discuss pimples of
Tata Elxi
A Mighty Then Wife Images of You Already Have
Been arrested in Tata Elexi and another
The company's next take on the industry in a still
From Packaging Sudheesh Companies Result B.Ed
Notes by Victim of Hatim Ki Duniya Hu
is from Mohali let me tell you one officer
Data from Capsicum World Have Even
Have Pimple Channel Certification and Register
r research and still want to present you
With Attractive Along with His Place
Industries Page Yes B R Not Go Into An
X result of Bachkar co in the history
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance
IT Security Dixit Bank But Kiss You
Are you having marriage in this company?
Can Reach Your Query During Presentation
Our students and already prepared in
Foreign Companies in Thought From It's Okay So
Let's Check Sanjeev and Recession Candy Crush OK
Thank you
that how is this Reshma Asha Karan Raj Jain
Arun Kumar on the bureaucrats of the opposition party
Amarnath Thakur Deepak Sharma Everyone Good
Morning Ravindra Kumar Jhanjhal Nishant Joshi
Arpan Rajput Indrajit Padhiyar Jigmi Door
Yes everyone good morning Jitendra Raghuvanshi
Vijay Choudhary and my friend Rakesh Malik too
From Kerala Good Morning Jitendra Singh
And now Praty Jalsa Nitin Maurya talks to everyone
I really enjoyed doing it Anil Wadhwa ok
For Dr. Hit Anil Desai, he wrote a
Apply Very - Clothing & S Usual
Wonderful and second Anil Bhai got a new name today
It has gone to me and Milind Bhai's
Captain and Vice Captain of Vijay Krishna Ji
Loved it or the name on one side of them
Capture Miliband and call him
Like
Vijay Choudhary ji came with his presentation
You are absolutely right Ravi ji Rajiv.
Sharma or
Come on Arun Kumar, the twin thing is good.
Chirag Bhai's OK Anil has a deep dress
If so, then presentation of HDFC Bank
Chirag Bhai gave it to me, I think
HDFC Bank has launched a Hunterrr to do this
It has been announced that it is worth Rs 50,000 crore.
Private Placement Refunds Will Be Raised
In the test market, Anil Pal ji's
The test is why fifty thousand crores
Press funds when they have quality lakhs
This is the lamp in the increased reserve of crores
Can you comment on this?
That Sir, as far as I saw, it was
Feedback This 15 Diamond Capital and Tattoo
Capital which is gram flour but we
IDBI and Vaibhav are accepted and
How fast he can get some tension from Arabic.
Timer to keep in capital and on Twitter
Even recently, this F above from that match
See but in the future so to be a teenager and
These people are taking out this fund to raise it.
I did it because if I tell my children
If he is transferred there, he will get the new
Cannot use a bank account for a loan
For this the receiver is back
I will explain and what happens in this bond
which helps in keeping the banking system in order.
To show the murderer a little
are contrasting to them
Come right, it is absolutely right, your lamp
Might as well be an alert for my brother and me
Chirag is there because login in HDFC Bank
Point dress will do something in the rest of the bank
I will have to do some fun race and HDFC
The cheapest bank according to its rating
The phone will ring and the rest of the bank will be fun race
Will go to do in which there are only a few 1pm banks
If it can also happen then they should have HD on their
It is not the doctor but the water because it is
Banking maintained leadership on the margin
And his religion is absolutely right brother.
Yes
That friend Jai Kishan ji, everything is fine, fine, fine
which I feel is that if I
I also look at US bonds last
Diet Means had doubled in the quarter
Expecting inflation to come in already
Swing and higher in future to that end
HDFC Bank MIC due to special
Testing in Next Lower Rates Facility
Tense Future of Birth Spread Ready
Expecting a to go for if oo
Torchlight somewhere for Kishanji and India
Let's be happy that Saturn is still
It has been told in the Monsoon Department that the
If the monsoon remains normal, we will be 90%
From 100 to 100, as happy as the monsoon
This time we will mix the crop that is already there.
This is going to be a life time high.
It definitely helps to reduce the information a bit.
It will be of good use to India if done correctly.
I expect ad as you guys did
Retail packaged and coming as is
This is also the expectation of the Monsoon Department.
How did it turn out? It well behaved very well.
Good indicator for India, reducing inflation
Thank you very much for your
And let's move forward to next
A very
Yes friend, Kumar ji said it absolutely right.
You also replied to Anil Pal ji.
and Arun Kumar ji or thanks Badal Pal
One More Time for More Portfolio Company
Chirag Bhai you are having the best vacation
Akhilesh Jitendra Raghuvanshi Ghuma Jitendra
Raghuvanshi doesn't know me directly.
I don't know that HDFC Bank, don't go to the
Jitendra Bhai has a request for you, bank.
He asked why the other banks did not apply it.
and I had to work on it a little bit, according to me.
HDFC Bank has subscribed or you
This can be done through a chart
If you can tell me this or tell me that it was night brother
The curtain is pulled aside here on HDFC Bank
that in November she said hi to the break
was around two thirteen hundred and after that when
Rekha De has given us the licking exactly the same
I have shown that the last two I will tell are bigger
Well done Chirag Bhai HDFC Bank
that he distributed so far so large
It was a good meaning of orange on 12th January
If I tracked it up, look here.
The chart from 2015 shows that
Just which one birthday before 15 is all
Things that are in the middle of 2019
It has been done and this time so the banking sector
It has a very long length
and type
I am seeing difficulty in this but as you
Told that by breaking 2,000 last year
It turned out that it was compared to this
Do it and make it clear to some people
A Real Charging Posture
Question Roy ok happy
There is one thing Chirag Bhai, I can see it.
This is the IP of 2015, someone had come
Bank online in 2015 Ashok Bhai
The Twenty15 thing is there, yes, a little bit.
This is a crying time for ICICI Bank.
I stopped and he came back to his five year old self.
HDFC Bank money was raised
It was not there when sister
nothing little it was a mantra meaning it
You can understand that do this then there is Bhrigu
that yes here play this great 2015
Both of them had it or Pimple also had it from static
Okay, so look at this, arrest clear but home
It is known that HDFC is white
Lily of performing Reserve Bank is not a
And here the second thing you get in subsidy is
Hafiz ji's head will be seen every two-three days.
Dieting in the year I get there
Was there a salary problem? It's a good one.
In 2014, it was impossible to see such a phone in speech.
Who has not got SSC exam, will do 340
127 The flower will bloom again, reviving its old feelings
I will pay a little tax and then I will get the old notes.
Cartage will be seen there in such
Take it as if this was the last time I called.
That was in 2008, everyone knows this.
I did it and that means there is a big reason
It is required there and inspection of animals
I can therefore rightly say that it does and a
The thing and the foot are also visible in the west.
Chirag Baitha has been selected as the ICC Bank Player of the Year 2020.
In fact, he reached the breakout level.
It is 2013 that he had fired that pack
Ashok Bhai was lying on top, if I give dowry
One will educate you about the exam results.
Jhaal
That you S6 Plus pimples not on the stomach
Now he is following it in his words also.
Come and get this at your home this year.
Or equal and this and any death all comments
Do it and tell me so that the idea becomes clearer.
Ujjain from the third bank because it has Ashok
Kotak and Tomato Printers in Band Competition
Check out this recipe
that any ho IGI with letter T
ok then
that it was developed in such a way that when the Pacific
It is amazing
has to take a very strange chance
No, may the one above be blessed
If yes, then we have to take the memo, then
Many times stop thinking that big banks are small
If you take it, then see, it depends on HDFC.
What is the difference between ITC Bank and Bank?
I am from Jaipur ICICI and HDFC
Given on the back foot but completed from the other side
The introduction of saints and sages takes place in the soil
It seems to be of 2000-2005 level.
ko tight very bad 16 low achievement radhe
Nitin Bhai, I think your career
Useful that HDFC Bank is doing pom pom
Guddu is using this thing in the bank meaning
Question Bank
Torch light thank you very much Chirag Bhai and
Ashok Bhai Spoil Sport in Gond Square
Thank you let me write the next query.
I, Jitendra Singh Arya, have asked about such
Lambagad in Arun inch and here incoming major
Text please advise Mayank Bhai that I
I'll go test any inverters here and
Which places will Uber be available on Tuesday?
Where does your income come from and which of your considerations
Was
that when the general store and anyone in it
There is a company, they have two Arvind suits.
One is the one who is earning from the PM, whom
We are proving cross premium wrong.
We invest in this opportunity around the world
These investments are made in the debt market
because they need liquid and all that
lives and according to IRDA some people
also live and this equity and these too
If you invest, then this time from here also
We do not tax their total income.
Because it can activate investment
Premium Growth on Key Corporation A Major Sales
Their point is that they have my business.
That's why I got a tractor and total income.
Nakul Soap has written that this year he has earned around crores.
Noida growth has been noted, total income has come
I mean this time they have to invest everything
Apply good pressure to the writer because its
Bad About
Queen Lover Point was matched and
Compression was selected and happened last year as well
The festival of death took place there on this income.
Thi a complaint today finish this year and in
So it looks a little bit automatically greased.
There is an increase in investment in the house
If it happened then it also started coming positive and
Jitendra Bhai asked that if too much
If their income here is Rs 400-500 crores
If it is there then it is not much, it is not normal
Only Jitendra Bhai, I am giving this other to you.
Income which includes foreign exchange and
Hai Investment Income From School Life Love
So how much cornflour is there in all this stuff?
So nothing if these cups so you
In which does normal live, I think
What inflation told you: two incomes, not one
Result
Actual boy to bank brother new money system
I am coming and tell me which other company
investment an investment in when it
Now you can club both the incomes and get the bill.
Yes, but Mayank Bhai won the Bigg Boss premium
To determine how much proper new blood is being taken
From this we can know that the higher the premium
Will this much income come in the future?
investment will be required because their
Youth is increasing but I have backed down
Like the side then premium insurance
Companies reached near take care new
How much premium the company is able to source
For the no data you gave and my
Carefully people's life and general desk
It must have become very clear, okay, thank you.
Thank you
I Anil Pal This festival is an ancient book
You are the best result, thank you.
Anil Bhai, yours
But such students are also found and all
The teacher doesn't have it so good, right?
Let Me Mood Next Query Prashant Khare
Wonderful presentation for a Chal by Chirag
Jain Bhaiya or Prashant ji OK A Grade Vijay
Brother nice post Jai Kishan ji Jai Kishan ji
Vijay Bhai told you, right?
A Large Brahmavaivarta Purana Brahma At This
Writing from Products Battle Heart
from lots of people in companies running to
Three Earths and Welcome Back to This Previous
Two three layer price told the wrong secret
Brother, this does not happen at all and this
Don't expect every company to last two or three years.
It moves on and then comes back to the old wound.
That's why those people think so, Raj Bhai
Because those people invest in such companies
Now you do it like you would do at any bank.
Show us the chart, now we can make PC like a bank
If you invest in companies, have expectations
He will rally back in two-three years.
This is for you on HDFC Bank
Questions page add in good companies
When investing, don't expect that every
In two-three years, you will become Ravan.
New Delhi Joshi Lalit Joshi who is back
His career is insurance and MC.
Which is good Sector-2 have for long term
Because both depend on discretionary income will
Going to grow in India to Jai Kishan ji's
I take this question to my side and
Chirag worked on insurance with care
Jai Kishan to brother and Chirag Bhai now both
Lalit Bhai's question is that I
I invested money in insurance so that we could
invest money because both sectors have their
We run according to people's savings.
what do you guys say
Sir, that is a very good question and it is helpful.
Okay Irritable 512 Ko First Word You Want
Meet to answer reminder backwards
I come in
Nothing OK file said very 10 sectors
Growth factors of field under Pandey Peth
There is growth in both these sectors in India and
Even if you have seen in this interview of
This year's mystery is solved because
Difficult for Him Even at Stupid Questions
Exam Me Question UP Alok Patel And
Sacrifice Who Sacrificed In India V2
The liquid and second to invest in this
Sector Sudhi Sectors Will Benefit in Love Oo
Yes, your language is absolutely correct.
You also researched this penetration
But named NS but you know such
I can also reduce both of them to nine.
Better and same penetration in C also
Currently, there are only total demat accounts in India.
Meaning it is only around five percent
In our India, there is a use judge there too.
What Shankar said is absolutely correct.
It has to happen, but let us keep these two things separate.
Look, you can see that here
The insurance part is the most difficult part.
that every dramatic Free City and subconscious
This will happen with Kovid and all this awareness is coming
This is in those people who are from our parents
Young generation like us came on awareness policy
Now this is what you thought was important here.
There is also a white on the same side as on the wards
He became a billionaire by investing in Jio 4G.
Also we can see HDFC AMC
The body speed is like that in 1617 means
Now we have invested in that thing here.
If we could see then this is the perfect cancer that we
Both sides and locations should be kept
Therefore, it has been clarified that this
in the sector
How to meet the pile of Fun Valley
That man bike I think both are good
and should invest in both
But don't forget general insurance.
Needed because general insurance needs
Just like the number of people who faced the challenge
The virus has done a lot of damage in this sector.
And growth will be visible friend solar bike
in both the bottle goods sector and now
Little by little milk lineage certificate on it
If possible, both of them will get proper education.
Tract
I, Sandeep Lanchit and Prashant Khare both
This old man and Jaikishan have said that you have done a lot
Well conducted or Eastern
Priyadarshini is so eastern, global very
Eager for adultery is falling apart
Activated sleep in which is related to
IT Industry Staff and Chief and Defame
Not from kurmi dating with answers in
Given behind the viral news of English semolina
Tithi Yadav Phone After Result Even In Quiet
Difficult to give correct something
Let's go and do vegetable typing.
Mera Tab Do They Want You Dance Latest 308
Correction definitely up android market
Latest Spot Market OK Very Difficult
For Any One Offers Pay or Paya What We Do
Substitute Term and Long Term Friends
Bodh 30 Company Switch Expect Him To Grow
15152 20% if 34 from some you coming down
And Was Hurt After His Death Kind of Increase
3 Price Range Way To Obscene Pcs Even
For a got the right 305 to 0.22
Opportunity Slowly Ends in the Future
Definitely Compound Wealth and Decorate
Corruption bow down Kishan ji Ashok Bhai Airtel
It would have been better if the chart of had opened or
I Think All the Stock Markets Are Ginning Corrections
Sleeping village suggested by some friend
Platform but not lower level RTI
is unlucky
A vacation key now set and correction the part of.
The market is no big deal.
You will need to be prepared for any
At least 25% to Media Good Company people
So if there is a completely normal correction then right now
Madam, you are saying that the stocks should be done and
But they can see even until now they have not seen
The form in it is still to be always
Prepared for collection of twenty five
A Big One on Percent Delivering Gold Clock
Products Very Good Company
I am Manoj Goswami excellent sir yes thank you
You are very much Manoj my Patharpratima ji good
Morning this noose ji Prashant Khare ji
Zinc Presentation by Team in the Future
Why Reflection That's Wonderful Teaching
Krishna Ji peels off the lamp 121
Presentation ok thank you all and let
The number of check iftekhars in the month became 12.
According to, yes, many excellent
Presentation ok kha Anil Kumar ji perfect
Jai Kishan ji Arun Kumar ji ok
That Mehul Bhai, wonderful presentation Lalit
Joshi HDFC Bank Account Leveling
Can I get a chance right now?
Look Lalit Bhai, just a minute later, the light has just turned on
Explained that the ICC is at the old record level
The bank has come, why did the full HD BP not come?
Because a strong company is
Less supply tight than others at the time of breakdown
But when it was time to walk, the first thing to do was run.
Under this, former Vijay Sahni has launched Shaurya Women
IDFC First Bank Inside Business Model In
The future prospect of an Arab IDFC
Can you tell something about the bank or chart pit?
If this continues, then it is a matter of time that
Actually I already Ready First
Milk was taken from her first
I did research on the course when I did it.
About a year ago in Egypt when the time
Data is not an exam, read one.
Your Ashok Bhai IDFC First Bank Do it
The lamp of the journey, brother, could also tell him this
I need a solar rock
loot effect what happened to it that it
Time I strengthened him that Nakul track
I had done it then for the last one year he
He had set a target and is going to do this.
The target on people is that first their
Retail has the highest allocation in the sector
The sector has to pay their loans, not return them.
Rice was some bad loan, we then he from this time
had to be removed from another route and his
I had to take it in reply but the most profit
paired with submit he then discovers that
When there is C, then in the future there will be no specific
This is true, shift it
That it became the same thing as this movie
It happens that some new star is taken
He would have said that this would happen later on when Salman Khan would first win.
If Congress gives the movie then it is better than that
Salman Khan first ghee
Also see the chart of phone number valve, it gives
Chirag Bhai, the IP of 2017 is not there yet.
It came back in 2017 15
Rupee Abir is recovering as soon as it
Purusha Vyapari Vary Dhanurveda and HDFC
The bank is in correction mood after rally and
Idea free first bank so old shock right now
Sir, they got OA grade from what was there in 2017.
I did that then the entire bank and side but
This is not the best so why invest
Plate this, you are my first profit, brother.
If they have launched it yet, then
Look, you could have kept it for five years.
Dividends are also not available in the coming times.
Every person will definitely perform in it but
Your first priority should be HDFC Bank
should do the same in Iraq
I will take a toy with me, thanks Chirag.
that your end that eastern academic your answer
No, Deepak Sharma, thank you very much
Prakash etc. Thank you Yours Anil Pal ICC
Lombard promoter reduces shareholding
Act in Itself and Techniques Front
Mez Okri shares have been reduced slightly.
Negative on other districts route of promoters
Impact Man Bike Jhal
that every time the question is raised again or
Promoters reduced their holding slightly
Has Rafi Kumar said anything negative about it?
Impact
A new one, with no definite negative effects
It will not happen because there are some rules which remain
It has to be done as per IRDA.
And also to do one race sir because
Actually, now the time for Kuwait has come.
It is important for them to score some points
part because provisions mean clean pa
Can there be some for this?
We shouldn't have a problem, the other way around
x is positive in any form
What can you do right now to make it 1 minute?
The situation is such that inflation and share holding are increasing.
Tell me something, I'll just tell you
39.20 20% held by promoters 10 minutes
Slide Celebration Patti from Face is 39.98
has 11.28 Don't Institutionalize
Investors have 11.23% of the government's
Pass point is 6
that a public has thirty-two okay happy
There is someone to give, no need to worry Anil
Brother, look, you should not have been such a type of tuition.
How to raise funds in India
It's such a big country, such a big function
If there is a chance, then reverse the money also.
I will have to worry about everything
Let's Lit Motors Next Query Akash Vakil
Prakash Bhai who is from Surat is very good.
Piyush Bhai from old friend in finance sector
I am losing percentage of my portfolio
HDFC Reader's Note Bajaj Finance Reader's Note
No, the only light to do this is Bajaj.
Finance is also a reader of HDFC reader.
What has become of Finance Minister RC Pathak now?
Why don't HDFC and Bajaj do this?
Finance is the final sector of both the apps.
there are companies so if both of you have
Increased fiber in both the fifth and
Set alarm clock in phone and rec
The reader has no business even if you oppose it.
You will get it, if it was feeling so good then one
Person is also equal
That and Bandhan Bank also have to be taken IDFC Bank
There's a way in I don't
Why have you kept it as Rabbit, make it HDFC
Bandhan Bank is equivalent to Bank if you like
If you do it then it is not equal to me to follow you a little.
There is too much light brother, so give it a little
adjust so that other emerging sectors
I can invest money like Vijay Chaudhary and this
Rumor or Keep Interrupting Just and Come Back
To ICL se long shareholding sorry
That is the Sunnah of ICICI Lombard
The promotion expressed I Don't Think That
Film Delhi-6 Date Picker 61.80 to 1000
Wrong Mins Ko Latest 30 Se Zoom But Ka
promoters folding presence is that
is dutiable
That you had done some of your dialogues
Most placements are in the last quarter
But this happens to some extent in normal circumstances.
Till then he gave a lot of holding and then he
Some tech gave me my fundraiser and it became a quarter inch.
There is already nothing wrong in such a bank
had sold his stage and was on such a bank
By the time the account was gone, Saif had no time.
Here too f5 time is lost or ok
You are right, thank you very much Jai
Kishan ji and Prakash bhai, I have hope
That yours is clear Vijay Choudhary Premium of
The Year More Than Life Last Year But Less 2019
You are absolutely right Vijay Bhai.
Premium Lifetime Not Hiten and Oil
Vijay is keeping his athleticism completely eagle-eyed.
Write this quickly in 1000 on Events General
These are all things every company should consider.
I am after both negative and positive
A side of the scientist Purvi Priyadarshan
The person is what should be weighted who gets the fruit
Edit SATI Tata Elxsi Rupee Mobile TCS
Divisional Volume Mi Full Song Purvi Madam
Representative on Apple OK if new
Company NTT on this tweet St and Chief now
Whereas in TCS we had invested so much money
I have put 527 on the set for so many days
2% of the forest is not very large.
The weightage of the director of the people, Madam Next
This is the presentation of Jaan Lijiye, this form of
Stop Mind Against Percentage 2% in
That TCS told you sick person 527
Percentage Investment King is a small company, good
Company Additional Person Alka Mia1 Percentage
Not much, madam, okay, because of Al Qaeda.
If you take a divide in the sector, then there
4% to 5% can be applied like this
and other items Madam Jitendra Singh and
which performed on Thank You Very Much
Jitendra Ji Pramod Gangurde Slam
Presentation Thank you Pramod ji Yeh Rishta
Thank you madam, yours sincerely, Brahmavarta Surya
Purchase at Removing Clothes End of the Nation
I will read it, Raj Brahma Bhatt sir, how
Many players will invest in any
Particular complaint to create one of its
In response, this Kishan ji from Jackie Chan's film
Raj Babbar asked me how many years I am
You should invest if you want to create wealth.
if so
Bluetooth setting ka sab jitendra for
Investing in Gupt Stop You Can For
Dates for life time ok henik rather
Porn compounding and through your wealth ok
Against like TCS TCS's turnover
The net is higher today than it was 10 years ago.
There is profit and this lion thing is going to give you a doctor
Mittal ji also said that whatever happened today is his
Turnover is its net profit for 10 years ahead
Hoga Ok Khush Shift Company Water Navodaya Win
Today Suvidha Net Profit Hai Yes Hens You
Can you imagine the wealth creation life in a
Looter Ejection ji and me to everyone
Request that so many new investors join
Which are starting from the market
3rd College Secure Portfolio Ready
Why do we see plus or minus again and again?
live because in 3 years of typing
You are not going to be like that when you start
What would you be doing with yourself for three years?
Different companies have adjusted their
Staying in place and during initial three
Years for investment in don't chuckle and
Portfolio Regular If You Are Right Now In
Visitors to Profit Will Give Me a Boss
to go to St. Paul's School at least 25 times a day.
Slide the song on the occasion and play it for 30 minutes
We get happier when the rally is over
Come and get confidence, check it again and subscribe.
Part plus and 500 normal thing you and
don't worry come
Similarly, after passing the first 3 years
After you are going to Jaipur flight profit
You will see what is the meaning of wealth in the wealth
The investment I've made will last me a lifetime
There comes a time when we should start meeting.
Just remember one thing for those with minimum 10 years
Money in less than 10 years
You will not get profit, you will get wealth
It won't work, still I have one more thing for you.
I would like to tell you friends, how to make real money
Need to rest for 10 years also
This is not what he wants this time.
Voting and mommy-daddy from day one first
From the year you start getting up to 6
Shares that are not traded in the stock market
Supply chilli in the market from the first year
Getting the card starts right
In which the debt cardiff is received and the remaining money is deposited.
meets the definition
84 promoted places in two-three years so you can invest in FD
So anyway those who are coming close to you and
And which joint is the referee for putting money?
Or else do stock market instead of FD
Your investment of Rs. 1000 will come back in 3 years anyway.
So after three years you have
The computer is yours, you're already overtaking it.
Diya hai so no need to worry yaar ko * create
Huge Wealth in Stock Market Justification
If you want then thank you Jai Kishan ji and
Expect Yamraj ji got his job and
Vijay Sahni ji, thank you to you too Sharda
Sharma and
How much is Next 9 News in the area?
If you want to keep percentage then after history
Who had kept it today, Atal Bhai?
I have a meeting right now but this is about sewing.
In turn, the unknowable
Who is the education ji, I would like to ask someone Jai
Kishan ji, how much weightage do I get in the IT sector?
should be kept in IIT especially Vijay Kishan
I will tell my full ID brother also, I will not
This also means naukri.com is also like this in IT
It comes but we only offer IT consultants.
Today we will talk about the rest of the IT sector.
How much money do I earn in consulting an advocate?
Kishanji IT Consultant Research
In the center we see the Front 7.5 Portfolio
10th year and has been discussed like
Five percent of the PCSN alarms 2%.
Been Arrested Traffickers Dish to Aadi Hai
Invited Best Companies in This IT
Consulting Sector 9
Hey friend, thank you very much Sanjay
Yes Anil Pal, congratulations on your last comment
Paul Team Captain Vice Captain Master
Blaster and Motivated User Thank You
You couldn't get anything from my dedication.
Because all these people have told me how much
Look today, all those people among you who
Did you present him like Faisal Bhai today?
The leaves at the Dual Religious Hospital of
You are liked and the presentation is done.
an hour's a lot because they say it's a
Why should I invest an hour for 5 minutes?
Tell my 5 minute people that you did well.
Watch intraday videos accordingly
The 5-minute people need someone for Wales.
There is no work, friend, I will not invest even an hour.
I can look and I hope
I will invest for 10 years, it is possible
Hetal Bhai made this presentation for Tiffin
Note Pro
that they collected so much data at least
It would have taken three to four days to store the data.
Rectified the data and decorated it for you people
He took the platform and returned to the hospital
I moved to Chirag Hill who lived in Rajkot
I am working in the bank Bank of Baroda.
March ending was I don't believe that
Rajpal ji, this March ending, all this was easy.
Collecting data with your team
communicating and today while he returns to his
He had gone to his village and had gone to his home from there also.
He did a presentation with you guys.
If you make perfect coordination then everyone is
Dedicated and what does this mean, please tell me
Everyone's commitment, if you do it, Minister.
Can Do It Everybody Started
One day he too had decided that I and
Look how well they are progressing
Big T-10 cricket wealth towards now no one
You also go from the background
That now this committee comes from some research of India
Your definitely any tubewell then next
Next Week We're Going to Discuss Two
Companies but next week there is a little change
Now let us discuss Tata Elxsi first in the 90s.
Will give 930 second link for 15 minutes
You will get as much as any other company L&T
Oh, I forgot his name, just let me check.
what was the name India List Play India
Thanks for reminding me to waste
India, we will discuss at 9:30 and
The first 10 will receive a third Very Special
So these three links will be available to you on Monday.
Get connected with fluoride will be updated
Close Loop Me Just Check Gaurav Shop Gaurav Ne
Told how to look at the pharma sector
Should and Master is not performing sector
definitely not
and when the issue arises, a
You will also upload it that we folded it.
I have set a lifetime high back in 2015
We were in trouble since 2017-18.
The momentum came back and this time it was called the lifetime of
If imposed, get ready for the pharma sector
Companies are also going to invest for the last time.
and the conversation about it is about pharma
Only U M SBI will do about the company
L&T ITC Art Bluechip which have been
The Top Wealth Destroyers in the Last 10th
this is
How can you say just one will create
Wealth in Take Care is exactly the right thing
Mahesh Bhai, at least I told you 10
It is important to invest for a year but you can stay here for 10 years.
Will I do this mic if you dickens sector
I will apply it to clean stomach and apply it to Scorpio
It is not necessary that you do it through gangsters.
If you invest money in it then it will be of Kaisan Ribbon or you
You will get condition tweet and money worthy songs then
Mahesh Tomar ji, we are confident that SBI and ITC
Biggest Balance Destroyer
I can't say every song, why not?
can because both companies have definitely
Reduced the pressure of file destroy in
done in either of the two companies
You invested money 10 years ago and today you have
Money has grown since then in both companies.
You've got consistent mails
I'll admit that Destroyer has a few more kernels.
that aloe has not made money then
Because it is only banking growing sector
There was no shortage of money, it was
You must understand that it seems to be
She blends that too that Rohit is not there
Mahesh Bhai is necessary to make money
This mic in anger and quality night
I hope to bring you back again and
We'll be back next Sunday and a new sector.
And until then with the results of new companies
That if the results of all the companies come,
If you have deep links in the companies also, then the links
Now put that very in that link.
in advance so that we can help you right away.
Shot Jackson Jain will also see Hungry Mary
A question, Chirag Bhai, Mayank Bhai, Hetal
Bike thanks to everyone I have a very much
A Prinsloo Every Work Even for Shop Boy
Death By Tarun By Check Complete Pradakshin
Thank you for decorating your thank you